This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Bucky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from his crew, Luffy and his newfound cohorts
have hijacked a Navy ship in order to rescue his brother Ace,
who's been transported to Navy HQ for execution.
You've been condemned in your sentences final.
There is not but despair on the path before you, however you may struggle.
Can't you see you're wasting your time?
All filthy criminals such as you,
the gates of justice will never open!
You're sure you want to open the gates of justice at a time like this?
All this time and you knew!
I got you!
You silly man!
Come on!
Answer me!
This is it!
The gate's about to close!
We have...
to go!
To make you!
The gate is closing!
Keep firing!
Take them out!
Any last words before I eliminate you?
Have at me!
Luffy has successfully broken out of the world's most impenetrable prison,
Impel Down.
Although, the end of this battle is nowhere in sight.
To the Navy headquarters!
Off to rescue Ace!
Living dangerously is one thing,
living carelessly another.
If I'd lack the foresight to bring an antidote,
I'd be stumbling over your corpses right now.
Don't ever underestimate Magellan.
Ha ha ha ha!
But we're here!
You shouldn't dismiss your own inclusion.
Your presence is a factor in our fate as well.
Though, he's right.
I was sure I was a dead man.
We're lucky we're all...
still alive.
Well, it ain't up to us whether we'll ever die.
Fear of death is the fastest way to lose.
See, ha ha ha!
Just live what you can,
even if it kills you.
Right?
See, ha ha ha ha!
Still, don't think I ain't grateful for your help.
Because I am.
And again, welcome to our gang.
I bet we'll make a great team.
I don't see much future for myself in this crit.
You're exactly the sort of person I've wanted to meet for some time.
See, ha ha ha ha ha!
See, ha ha ha ha!
Gather round, men.
The time has come.
Let's raise a toast to our unprecedented escape from Impel Down!
To us!
Damn, what is that?
I'm afraid we'll have to do without Inazuma from here.
Wait, are you trying to tell us the infection is that serious?
I was lucky that Magellan hit me with only one type of poison.
I was able to flush it out of my system using my healing and energy hormones.
Hee-haw!
It's an ambivalent fix, though.
One hormone will take years off my life, while the other causes severe side effects.
So for him, the best thing possible is good old-fashioned bed rest and natural rehabilitation.
Nothing can help you to regain the years lost by using the hormone Inazuma is an indispensable newcomer of the Revolutionary Army.
We need him healthy, so we have to make sure he recovers slow and easy.
Now that I think about it, he wasn't such a pain in the butt after all.
He was such a good guy, and he got God-saving us.
Brother Bon!
Hey, come on, guys.
It's sad and all, but you can't waste your whole life's mourning.
He was great, but now he's dead, and that's the way it is.
So all he can do is party.
That's what he would want.
So there you go.
It can double as a funeral for Mr. Two.
Oh, Christ!
Hey, for all we know, there's still a chance Bon didn't even get killed, you big nose.
Oh, hey, what did you just say to me?
You've got a big, stupid nose to go along with your big, stupid face.
Oh, how about I stretch your stupid face until it's...
Oh, blew it out your giant nose.
If you ask me, they both look like idiots.
Fancy trick how you rallied those sharks.
How'd you do it?
I was under the impression only mermaids have the ability to speak to fish.
But that impression is clearly incorrect.
Is that odd?
A fish man being friends with fish?
Well, it's not the usual, I know that.
You're a strange one, huh?
A misfit of the savage species.
Fine, I'll take that as a compliment of sorts.
Yes, it's true.
Fishmen do have a violent nature.
Bon is not dead, damn it!
Whoa!
Captain Buggy threw another big red nose!
Luffy.
Huh?
I wouldn't be here if it weren't for you.
You gave me the chance to rescue Ace.
And I owe you a great debt.
Don't think about it like that.
We're even.
And besides, you're super strong.
I'm just happy to have you on the team.
I wish I could thank him properly.
And apologize for my involvement in that unfortunate situation.
But no, this isn't the time.
We have enough to worry about for now.
I only hope my strength will be enough.
I may be one of the seven warlords,
but they'll strip me of my title after this.
Now let's make Navy Headquarters regret the ever laid hands on Ace.
We must do right by our fallen.
We'll make your friend proud and rescue Ace at any cost.
Warlord Navy Headquarters?
What?
Oh, really?
You're seriously a warlord?
Geez, no wonder you're so strong.
Yes.
I suppose I should have told you sooner.
Everybody else knew that.
Hey!
What's all this talk about Navy Headquarters?
Don't tell me we escaped from the bowels of hell
just to head straight back into the jaws of the beast!
I'm afraid so.
Screw you!
Nobody is that crazy!
Surely you guys heard about the war brewing between Whitebeard and the Navy!
Uh, war?
Navy Headquarters.
Don't act like it's a big surprise.
Not our fault you're so dense.
Say what?!
Well, we passed through the Gate of Justice.
Isn't that right?
Our destination is Eni's Lobby or Navy HQ.
This tub current is restricted to government passage only.
It's one giant whirlpool that connects the government's three major facilities.
The reason we bust it out now is because we have a role to play in this war.
So you best get used to it.
Yeah, the real fight's about to start.
Real fight?
Then what you call it back there!
No way!
No way to tell us about this!
Stop!
Turn this ship around, you bastard!
Freeze!
Stop!
There's no stopping and there's no turning around.
Not while the ship's on the current.
If you're scared, just get off.
We can't do that, moron!
That would kill us!
We both have devil fruit power!
Navy HQ!
You, the warlords, and the white-beard pirates all fighting each other at once!
Nobody can survive that!
I've heard enough.
Please take me back.
I'd rather be in prison than this war.
All of us from New Common Land knew about this plan.
Then why the hell didn't you tell us?!
This is it!
We're all dead!
Mommy!
Hey!
What is that?
You guys hear it?
It's a transponder snail.
But who's calling?
Don't you get it?
Think!
We're on a Navy ship!
Huh?
Well...
What's this?
How was this?
It's a tapetang!
It's a Saiyan ship's army ship!
Scottie's Phi-
It's just that I know what's here.
Uh, hello?
He answered it!
Greetings, from Navy HQ.
Hey, Luffy here.
Idiot, don't say that!
Listen, kid, we're aware that the ship has been hijacked by escabies.
We received a report from Impel Down, so let's be honest here.
Before contact was lost, we had insider information being fed to us.
Based on this, we've determined who the two ringleaders behind the breakout are.
Two?
You, the pirate known as Straw Hat Luffy, and another notorious pirate, Buggy the Clown.
Eh?
Whoa!
Wait, what?
Ringleader?
Seriously?
We've got warlords here, and their main suspect is Captain Buggy?
Who the hell are you?
Come clean with us!
No!
Why me?
Pass me the documents.
Here.
Thank you.
At first, we just assumed that the clown was another two-bit criminal.
But to be frank, we were wrong.
We learned he was a crew member on the ship of Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Ah!
They found me out!
What?
You crewed on the Oro Jackson?
Unbelievable!
You're a star!
A star among pirates!
Oh, and there's one other thing.
He's an ally of one of the four emperors.
His name is Red-Haired Shanks.
Are you serious?!
So, if you can hear us, Buggy.
We don't know how someone with your background has laid low for so long.
But you most certainly stepped into the spotlight now.
Well...
We haven't defined your connection with Firefist Ace yet.
But we're sure you share the same goal with Straw Hat Luffy.
To rescue him from execution.
Not really.
We know that you're accompanied by Jinbei, Crocodile, Ivanka.
Not to mention the more than 200 average run-of-the-mill ruffians you tricked into following your lead.
Now let me explain your future.
Your fates depend on whether we open the gate of justice.
As long as we leave it closed, you can't get to Marine Four.
And you can't even get out of the tub current.
You will be completely stranded.
There is no sea for you to escape to.
Better get used to your surroundings.
That's all.
Hey!
Wait!
Navy!
I'm gonna rescue Ace no matter what!
Better keep your potatoes peeled!
Or what?
What?
The things keep your eyes peeled!
Now I'm gonna be craving potatoes!
Thanks a lot, pal!
He just tried to pick a fight with Navy HQ.
Forget the potatoes!
Wait!
I've gotta know, Captain Buggy!
Were you honestly a member of Gold Raunch's crew?
And a sworn brother of red-haired Shanks?
You should've said you're one hell of a pirate, Captain Buggy!
Now, hold on!
Aw, dammit!
The government's never gonna let me out of their sights now that the truth's out!
Not the background I was expecting from him!
And yet he's so weak!
That pedigree?
And he's so petty?
Every ship has one.
A little blemish, I mean.
Shut your mouth!
You know, actually...
Perhaps you've heard of a pirate named Buggy from the East Blue.
The old vice-captain guy said something about you.
Huh?
The vice-captain?
Yeah, the old guy, Rayleigh.
You know him, right?
Do I?
Are you saying that you've actually seen Rayleigh?
Aw, man!
I miss that guy!
Where'd you see him?
They're talking about Dark King Rayleigh!
Like it's no big deal!
Huh?
Holy crap, Captain Buggy!
I knew you were the genuine article!
No!
Look, not so fast!
Everything is true, yes, but you can't go spreading this around willy-nilly.
We gotta think about my future as a pirate!
Wow!
I can't believe you're a member of such a legendary crew!
Buggy!
Shut up already!
I was an apprentice, that's all!
Buggy!
You can't worship me for that!
Only there was some way.
If I could defeat Whitebeard,
maybe I could become one of the four emperors.
Hell yes!
Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I would need to become the King of the Pirates!
It's perfect.
Some of these guys have probably got higher bounties
on their heads than I do.
If I play my cards just right...
I can do this!
Captain Buggy, we'll follow you until the day we die!
Just give us an order!
Like steal this ship from the guys who stole it!
We don't have to go to Navy HQ!
That's right, and then we'll be free!
Sorry to do it, Straw Hat,
but we're taking control of this ship!
We already broke out of prison,
and we don't want dying to be the next thing we do!
Surrender now!
We've got Captain Buggy on our side.
Tell him, Captain Buggy!
Buggy, buggy, buggy, buggy, buggy, buggy, buggy!
Only one way to handle this.
Kill it.
Good.
I've got this!
I really think I could do it!
Buggy, buggy, buggy, buggy, buggy, buggy, buggy, buggy!
Buggy, buggy, buggy, buggy!
That's enough! Don't get too flashy!
You guys are high on power and acting impulsively.
No matter what, this ship's not stopping.
We're headed straight for the heart of the war.
And you guys are already on board, aren't you?
Think about what that means for a second.
In no time at all, we'll come face to face with a man standing with his foot on top of the world.
Chances like this don't come around more than once in a lifetime.
So listen, I want all of you to live out a dream with me.
For today, I'll conquer Whitebeard and thus rule the world!
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
Captain Buggy!
Thank you. The darkness of hell had beaten us down.
You saved us! Gave us life! We almost lost the most important thing!
Yes! Our dreams!
You've got us dream again!
I'll follow you anywhere, Captain Buggy!
To hell with living a peaceful life!
All right then! Let's win this war, you guys! To Navy HQ!
War! Buggy! Buggy!
So I guess the mutiny's over?
Then he's not entirely useless, I suppose.
You're gonna rule the world, Captain! I know it!
I'm with you to the bitter end!
That's right! You are!
Let them have fun while they can.
Huh?
The ship transporting Port Castilles will arrive at Marineford shortly.
Ah. Perfect.
Right this way! Please board the ship!
There's plenty of room, so don't worry!
We'll get everyone on board!
Prepare to receive the present arm!
Let the ship out!
Nami, traveling on the sky island of Wetheria, heads for the Grand Line.
but the pace of the island's travel makes it unlikely that she'll ever reunite with her friends.
Meanwhile, will Frankie be stuck as a tea-drinking gentleman forever?
On the next One Piece, the Friends' Whereabouts, the Wetheria Report, and the Cyborg Animals,
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!